grovemade.com 2013-05-25

# iPhone 5 Case and iPad Case by Grove | Grove

**As you browse  [grovemade.com](http://grovemade.com/), advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.   Our [display advertising partner](http://www.adroll.com/), AdRoll, then enables us to present you with [retargeting advertising](http://www.adroll.com/retargeting) on other sites based on your previous interaction with [grovemade.com](http://grovemade.com/). The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  You can [visit this page](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners' targeted advertising.**

**To Our Customers:**

Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. We respect your right to keep your personal information confidential and understand your desire to avoid unwanted solicitations. We hope that by taking a few minutes to read it, you will have a better understanding of what we do with the information you provide us and how we keep it private and secure.

**A. Types of Information We Collect**

We collect certain personal information about you – but only when that information is provided by you or is obtained by us with your authorization. We use that information to process your payments on Grovemade.com at your request.

Examples of sources from which we collect information include:

  * Newsletter subscription box
  * Payment check-out

**B. Parties to Whom We Disclose Information**

As a general rule, we do not disclose personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone. However, to the extent permitted by law and any applicable state Code of Professional Conduct, certain nonpublic information about you may be disclosed in the following situations:

To comply with a validly issued and enforceable subpoena or summons.

In the course of a review of our company’s practices under the authorization of a state or national licensing board.

In conjunction with a prospective purchase, sale, or merger of all or part of our company, provided that we take appropriate precautions (for example, through a written confidentiality agreement) so the prospective purchaser or merger partner does not disclose information obtained in the course of the review.

As a part of any actual or threatened legal proceedings or alternative dispute resolution proceedings either initiated by or against us, provided we disclose only the information necessary to file, pursue, or defend against the lawsuit and take reasonable precautions to ensure that the information disclosed does not become a matter of public record.

**C.  Confidentiality and Security of Nonpublic Personal Information**

Except as otherwise described in this notice, we restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to employees of our company and other parties who must use that information to provide services to you. Their right to further disclose and use the information is limited by the policies of our company, applicable law, our Code of Professional Conduct, and nondisclosure agreements where appropriate.  We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable laws and regulations to guard your personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or premature destruction.

Thank you for allowing us to provide exceptional, handmade products. We value your business and are committed to protecting your privacy. We hope you view Grove as a trusted partner and we will work to continue earning your trust. Please email us if you have any questions or if we can be of further service.
